<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cramer&#39;s Generator</title>
    <link>https://cramersgenerator.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cramer&#39;s Generator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cramersgenerator.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://cramersgenerator.com/about_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cramersgenerator.com/about_us/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you We sell, service and install standby generators. We also sell and service portable generators. We are a factory trained warranty repair center for Van Wert county and surrounding areas. Cramer&#39;s is locally owned and operated by Steve and Patti Cramer. Steve and Patti Cramer are lifelong residents of Convoy, Ohio and have over 25 years of experience in the parts and service business.
Our phone is always on!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generators</title>
      <link>https://cramersgenerator.com/generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cramersgenerator.com/generator/</guid>
      <description>Future home of generator products come back later and we will update this </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prices</title>
      <link>https://cramersgenerator.com/sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cramersgenerator.com/sales/</guid>
      <description>Are you in need of a standby generator? We will come out and walk you through from designing all the way through completion of the project. We custom design every project to the home and it&#39;s needs. We install whole house generators so that your whole house has power during a power outage event. Whether it be in the middle of the harshest winters or crazy hot summer Cramer&#39;s will be by your side to make sure your generator is functioning appropriately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://cramersgenerator.com/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cramersgenerator.com/services/</guid>
      <description>Do you need repair work? Whether you need repair services done in our shop or we come out to your property, Cramer&#39;s can repair your generator for you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>